Shōsetsu and Gikyoku
In April 2017, many young people with dreams and hopes came to our Soft On Demand again this year.
So this year as well
A survey was conducted on who should be the new female employee for all male employees
Today, I will talk about the shōsetsu and gīkyokus.
Today my teacher will whisper in your ear and tickle you a lot
The shāsetsu is a set of words that are composed to appeal to the reader
as he or she asks who did what where when in which place
10. Kiss me on the lips
So please feel good and show me your face
As a result
It is composed according to the intention of a person.
Every year, the results of the survey are divided into various votes.
11- Run your fingers through my hair
This year's result was very interesting that a certain female employee received many votes
She whispers gently like this
12, Touch Me
I recommend you to wear earphones or headphones when you go out.
So we decided to verify if the female employees who received many votes were really erotic
Three-dimensional and individualistic
13, Slowly
You'll feel much better!
I have to be clear about this, or else it's a waste of time.
On the other hand, novels are three dimensional an individualistic
The characters in them are also realistic
Excuse me
Many have drawn ordinary people
Yes
Then how do you read the novel?
I think about how to read a novel, the type of novel and so on.
I'm sorry to call you out of the blue.
Good morning!
Are you okay?
Do you think it is short story or long story?
Yes,I am fine
Sorry about this
History novels or modern novels
What are you going to do today?
It's not a bad story
Is it fictional work
Okay
Or do you thinks that this book has actual records
An interview
You're doing an interview in Shizuoka University right now
Yes
I'm doing it. Please look at my Twitter friends
Has it been a year?
This is from Yanase
It's been one year since the end of October, so now
You're preparing for it, right?
How many times have you done
Are we listening
I'm going to record a video of the bus making.
Can we do more
Yes
Please concentrate
Maybe in winter
Because there were about 50
Then next
A little more
60 to 70
We will explain how
So much
Then pro
For example Yanase-kun's girl or female employee will go there and experience AD
Not professional but did various things
Is there anyone who wants to read?
Today
There is a series where you meet and get attacked by an actress.
Like an experiment interview
If you don't mind
Would you like me do that
I've done it recently
Hey, what are you doing here.
Yes, yes.
Really?
I'd like to confirm your will so we're filming now
You haven't seen mine, have you
Inoue doesn't like it
What's that
Oh really?
It was normal
No one has ever seen me having sex with men
Please let me do it
He's not mad at me
Can you do it ?
We're just playing
Really
Right
I'm his best friend
But we did
I don't want to hear it.
Can you say the word apple in Japanese
Then please help us
You're making it hard for me to say anything!
Apple
No, we are not...
Ok
Hello, my name is Lena Miyashita and this is a home-study class
Anyway you two haven' t opened your textbooks yet and
Let's try
I'm really good at it.
Thank you
But there are a lot of difficulties because this is your first time
Nice meeting you
Do you have a script?
We are in the middle of a class right now
Do you understand?
It's like reverse prank
Yes
Please continue with your classes
I'm Yuto. Nice to meet you
Please
Yes, nice to meet you
If none one is concentrating
Sorry for the inconvenience
Can you do it ?
Then there's no way
Of course
Tell us quickly
Where are your parents?
We'll send it by e-mail later
You can
Sorry but can they concentrate
You can go back now
What did he just say
Today,I'll just play as much is okay
Oh really
Is it okay if they come in without permission
He's a good teacher.
I agree with you, he is really good at teaching students
The plan is
Invite her on a big location
You were better than him
And let'see how far she can do
Oh, is that so?
Yeah...I want to be like him
Then I'll interrupt you.
He doesn't know anything
Don' t listen what they say
That's the plan.
What?
Tetsuya is getting carried away
No
Do you think the teachers can not teach their students well
Yes
Have they taught them how strict adults are
Is it a crime?
How's it going to be okay
It's violence.
Please teach me how to do this!
Ouch...
What are you doing?!
You guys always get in the way of my class, don't you know that!?
Hmm ... in this case
Because the bottom of the song is a related noun
If you translate
This is such an inconvenience for us!!
Hey what are you doing??
The song his father loved was Pops
It will become an old pops
It was a problem.
So, based on what you've learned so far
It's good, isn't it?
try to solve this problem
Students and teachers don' t matter.
What are you talking about...
This is a human vs human fight between me and you guys
A fight...?
That sounds weird
I've been hearing that for quite some time now
I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but let me know in the comments.
Hey, you.
If it's a big mouse...
The next day
What are you doing?
It is small!
You're smaller than the big mouse
Good morning!
Yeah yeah
And I think this one is bigger
This question is kind of difficult
Are you OK?
How about yours
so do your best
Yes
What were you doing just now
I'm waiting for the next one.
I was looking for materials of actresses to shoot
This one also looks small
It'so small.
Oh my god!
I'm looking for a job.
She said she doesn't have a script today, so...
You have an AT company, but are you okay?
My mom asked me
and my friend'son
So you don' know what we're going to shoot?
How about you?
told him
No idea and she didn''t say that it'scene today
that I should teach him
but will he be able
You guys are crazy
if i teach like this?
Oh really
Your penis is smaller than this one
It's hard to be perfect...
But it doesn't bother me and makes my work easier
I'm nervous, but we have to do our best.
Well we can not 100%
Is it okay for you
Look, it is so small
Thank You
Let's go!
Are you doing it now
It looks fun
Even though your penis was small
Where are we going?
I'm going to take a close-up of you.
Then, solve the problem as it is.
Upstairs or take a shower
Did you bully her?
It's none of your business.
We'll shoot on the same day, but don't worry about it at all
Can i stay here
Let's do our best
You don't want that
You guys are embarrassing me...
No
I want to go.
Thank you
Go clean up the room!
Yes, ma'am
Do you need a shower?
Good morning
Here she is!
Momo is being bullied
You're in your best clothes
Yes.
I'm wearing a dress that is easy to move around in today'shoot!
What're you doing?!
It was an easy-to move dress
Is it the basic?
We'll start shooting soon, so please go inside and wait for us
I don'think so.
You don' t?
If she's like you, she wouldn''t have a girlfriend!
She would be pregnant by now...
Let me say hello at your room
Look at her now
She is getting bigger because of your words
This is my waiting room
Stop it
Good morning, sir
What's up
Are you there
Excuse me
Good morning.
What? Where have you been looking at since a while ago ?
Hey, don't come any closer.
Wait
You don't have time today
Excuse me
Don' close your eyes and look at me!
Sorry
Good morning
I'm Hanase from SOD Production Department
What
I dont want to see you
I've noticed from the beginning
You really dont?
Today, I'm going to do a lot of random things like this.
Today, as AD
There are some parts that we can't do
Thank you for your cooperation
Your underarm is saying it wants a peek
You were watching my erotic place all the time
Thank you for your cooperation.
Wait...
What are you talking about
All of sudden?
Yes all the sudden!
Come on let'see
I'm going to wear AD today, so please don't bully me because it's the first year of my career as an AD actor!
Good morning
Let go of my hand
Take it off, you pervert.
So suddenly
After all ,I'm interested in that kind of thing
It's almost our first meeting
Please don't be shy.
You can'take it off with that outfit?
Thank you for coming today!
But you know me
I guess there's no other way...
Me too
I'm Bibi Hansen.
Do you always think about erotic things and peep
You're smart, aren't you?
This is a classroom!
It has nothing to do with the classroom
A lesbian!
What are you doing?
Smart...
Let me see
I was so nervous...
Feels good
Do you always do this kind of exercise like that
You're moving
Let's go to the next job then
Next, let me show your room
No today it's like this
Then, show me how you usually do it.
Looking at my clothes makes you excited right
Good luck with your sleep
Let's cheer up.
No
Excuse me
Is your nipple weak
I'm Yanase from SOD Production Department
Today,I'll be your editor
Hey, don't make me do it.
What's the matter with you
I wont
What about you?
Thank you
Aren't embarrassed
Let's do it over there.
Over there?
You said that you'll look at my dick
It might be hard to do here
Are you ready?
I can't...
Do it properly
I'll look at it
Don' pull out your chest
Excuse us
Hurry up and show your penis
How was it? Were you nervous at all.
Two of us
I was very nervous, because there were so many men around me
It's a shame to have dicks
Ready, go
That's right
You should say that to a man
Hey
It must be hectic for you
Don' touch
Don'' t want touch and squeeze
Yes
Because we are quite busy
Don't you want me to rub your butt?
Please sit down
You're good at taking photos of people who are awake
Hey Sato-kun
Then, look at it there.
Do you know Yanase
He is going on the show today
Oh really
Nice meeting him
It is cute to be embarrassed
Look at my butthole over there
I don'think so, but if you have any problems with it.
How do you feel?
I feel so good.
It's okay to drop it a little bit
I'm holding your butt
So let'see if it can stand
While shooting the making of that
It's warm, isn't it
SOT DVD recording
This is the making
Thank you for your cooperation today
You can let me do this
Or do you want a scrub
Please leave
Thank you
Sorry for being busy
Follow Mr Kusawa
Don't be so proud of yourself.
Great
You have a penis like this
My back hurts
I'll do it with you two together
That much
I'm not sure if it's true or not, but we're going to check.
Hey, hurry up and pet the baby.
Feels good
We are going to do a pee-check now
Some of the people who came here today may have already peed
Stop it
Maybe my boyfriend is coming
But there are some who haven't
I'll look at you when you're petting a lot of things
So let me see if they did
You want us look at them?
I'm so tired.
It's hard to breathe...
Yes
This is an important job
Are you an athlete, Mori?
Yes
Let's go inside.
You're getting harder and harder
Your body is honest
Do you do what you want me too
Right?
Petting face
Stop
It's cute
Me
Are you happy now
No, not at all
No
You're happy to be petted by me, aren't you?
Does it feel good?
I'll take a picture of you guys
We're going to check if there are any people who have already left the room
You are excited because I rubbed your crotch.
More, more.
Would you like us help?
No!
Hey hey
Can i touch just for awhile
Over there
Let's do it more
Yasui, this way
You can use the trash that Yuki threw away
He goes first
Please take it off.
Look at there
What kind of Thai food do you like?
Something has grown
Do you know what will happen from now on
Is this okay for you now ?
Excuse me
Ouch!
Do you want me to help
Do you want me to help you?
Good morning!
Good morning again...
It's more painful than before.
I'll help you, so don't do it yourself.
You look like a baby.
Thank you
Do you want me to do it too?
Can I say that?
Don't come near me
No, you can't
You are Shizuha-chan
You have a stiff neck
Yes
How is it? Does your skin feel good and slimy ?
We have good chemistry
How is it now
Your face has become harder than before
I want to hold her
Get out of the way.
Do yo
You feel better, don't you?
No I don'
She is so cute
Thank you very much.
Say it again
It's not good
Then let's make your skin more moist
This is the last one, right?
Are you excited because your hair is falling down
Why?
Thank you so much!
Not at all
Yes I'm fine now
Wait a minute, please...
Is the moisture in the pores comfortable for you
Your hair was wet recently
So everyone's done with it
Oh my god!
Yes, it's okay.
It'so hard to breathe now
Everyone is ready so let us do our best for the next shoot!
Do your hair too
Stop
Thank you very much
It feels good
Don't stop it
Don't stop.
I'm happy when you look comfortable.
I can't do it anymore.
Your bladder is getting bigger and bigger!
Let us do our best
I'm sweating a lot now
Okay
It looks like a suit
We are in the same age group as men
Be more stiff?
So we will try to match
Me too
The girls' team it will get excited
Great
Okay
You're sweating
Ready... Start
I would like to invite the actresses who participated in this time.
What's this?
It's cold
I want you to do it more.
What's wrong, are you going to go already ?
You said be patient
Good morning
How are you?
Thank you
Yes, thank you
If you endure it will feel much better
It's getting harder and harder
Everyone
Hmm what
I'm going to have sex with you.
I'm nervous.
You're making a loud noise.
Do i look like your panties
You don't like it?
Well, you're so naughty.
I can not help it...
It's a success!
The tip of your penis is touching the mark
Let's do it over there, in the room over there
You can do anything you want here
Carry me
Is this okay with you now ?
Shall we carry you?
Wow!
We don't need any rubber bands
Then let me scrub your body again
Make it harder
My dick is getting harder and harder.
Stop it!
Your body is harder than before
Your dick is happy now
Sex is over!
After all ,I wanted to see your panties
Let me go
I want to have more sex.
Me too, but...
Should I do this faster?
Sex is over!!
Do you feel good
This one's Pepe'so let me do it for you
Stop
Stop it.
It looks like she is doing a rap
Here we go
Oh yeah
You are biting my ear, too!
She is doing rap
Can you see?
I was surprised.
Really
But this isn't good
It looks like a firework
It feels good?
Thank you.
Thank you very much!
I can't stop you from being bitten by my butt...
How was it?
Do you feel good?
It was a dream, wasn't it Mori-san
It's amazing...
I felt like a real person
This is my first time to see the live performance
Hey, you're slimy from the beginning.
Oh! It's gone
You are annoying
Did that make yourself feel good
Do you like this?
Did you feel better?
You should speak more
Speak more!?
Oh my god
There's a tissue here, and the trash is over there.
What is it
Are you feeling better now Shima chan
I haven't said that it's okay yet.
Yes
Let me hear your voice more clearly!
But both of us like it
Oh that was good
I know your face
Next preparation
I'm not good at this.
But, he is still very healthy!
Stop
The next day
Let me go
Yes
What?
Let me give you a little more massage
It's hot!
You are sensitive, Kintaro
There
Don't mess with me.
Good work today
I'm so tired.
What are you doing?
Organizing equipment
How do you like this kind of thing
We only have one girl
Behind
Turn around.
You're doing great!
Does it feel good
There, there!
So, I'm going to do AD work this time.
Did you get a good result?
It's also a report...
Maybe...
What is the meaning of AD work?
It's better to be tied up with your butt, isn't it!?
When you come here for hot springs
You have no choice but understand actresses' feelings
My victory is mine!!
Is that so
Then what about this
You did it yourself?
For example
Let me say stand-in
When they say what kind
Don' leave me alone
We have an explanation
Do you want me to do it?
At that time
I'll do it with you, or at the house like a little while ago
This feels good too
It's parallel to something like checking
Because there are also actors who don't stand up
Here!
Or care for such things
I've sucked it all out.
So how about this
So that kind of business will come out from this time
You feel better, don't you?
Do you hear it somehow?
Yes!
Do you want me to suck yours too then ?
Well then
There is definitely something embarrassing
Great
Wow, it's hard again.
What do you think of that idea?
I think so, but it's a job.
Wow, your butt is so sensitive
Let me do my best and let you go
Then what about this?
Then everyone can get the trust of girls
It's a good idea!
Can i lick your butt
May lick
Everyone will rely on you
Stand in order
Yes!
You're standing up straight!
If there is anything else
Please call
There's a mole here
Do your best
This is the best.
You have a sexy face again
It is hot
Good morning
It'so hot.
Did you want to put out your teeth again by any chance
Do you want me to rub more?
Thank you very much!
Natsume-san?
Thank you very much
I don't want to hurt myself.
Yes, it is OK
Well
I'll count ten so if it becomes zero
Here we go
It is okay
Hey!
You sound like a girl
It feels good
Oh, my God...
So be patient until then
What should I do!?
Otsuki san
What does this mean?!
You're so excited
This is a big problem
It's like this.
I'll do my best.
If you want to take part in the bus tour, you have go over the bridge first!
Here we go
It's been a long time since the last time we did this exercise together!
What did she say?
As I said before if you want take part in a bus tour
Ten
Go over that bridge
You can do it by yourself
Jump off
Human horse
Can you let me continue?
Thanking
Good job
No, no
You are grumbling
Halfway there.
I want to take off my clothes
Yayyyy!
Wait a minute.
Thank you very much
I wonder if it's here...
You're the biggest mouth I've ever seen.
I have a license to do this massage.
It was not there
Yes, please give me space
You're almost there?
What's that?
You don't even know a woman's body, but you say big things all the time
When you get your license, it comes with you
It is in the real center mode
Just a little more, so hang in there!
No
It was the first time for me too
Oh yes
But you do
Thank you
Then please
We're going to play a game now.
Please
This part is good
Please look at the board, everyone!
I'll teach you.
Game
Let me show you more
Yaya-san will do it for us in Mogi
One, two...
Can you show your dick?
Sorry
Feels so good
Let's go one by one
It is our job
Good luck!
Great.
Oh, wow.
You were able to bear it properly
Please shake your body.
Shake, shake...
Do you want to rub it with this?
I want you to lick me too
Did you feel good?
Yes
With both hands
Can we do it again?
Yes
Hurry up because we're in the middle of a shoot
Yeah
You want, don't ya
Now you'll be shaking
But I gave you twice and still so hard
I don't know how it will turn out but
I think you're going to lose.
It feels good
If you want, we won't let you go in one by one
You're breathing
Why?
Because it feels good
Because we could endure
Because if he goes in there's no way out
A little more
Drink it.
How is it
So when it comes down on him
He has a chance of getting away
But once this guy leaves
Chinko is happy.
You can still win
As a reward
She's happy to be rubbed by my Manko
I'll lick
It means that the chances are high
Yes
I see.
Did you revive?
Yes, yes
Don't you want to taste the inside of Mankos?
Can we take a picture with you guys
Please
Don'tell your mother.
Thank you
It'so good
How is it
Good
It'so slimy.
So good
I'll put you in the bowl, okay?
I'm not sure if it's going to work.
It won't come out because we're doing a live broadcast, right?
We haven' noticed yet...
Excuse me!
The real thing is about to start so please move back together with us for now
It feels good, doesn't it?
How do you feel?
You can feel it even if it is just a little bit right now
Game ready
Start
Your chinchin is very warm
I'll show you where your blood is.
I can not put this in my mouth!
I'm going to eat it.
It's getting puffy again
Try to chew harder than I do.
Please blame me later
Please take it off.
See?
Does it feel so good
I'll take it off because you're hot
Wow!
Chew, chew...
Do you like the teacher
Cut!
My Manco
Can we move on to the next scene?
Taste it more
Come on
Please lie down here, three of you
Make your butt hard.
Next is a game where they have to chew oranges fast
You are too good attacking
Where's Erii-san
Coming back
I'll eat it.
Please wait a moment, we will press the button
Which team can eat more mandarin?
It'so hard
The woman should put the mandarin in her mouth
More!
Harder
So how about this
This man wants to have some mandarins
Do you want some mandarins!
Let me have them
Let me eat it!
Do more
Let him have a bite of the orange.
He'still eating it?
Orange, orange...
Orange-orange
I want to give you some
Give us some
Delicious
Wait
That was what we did
The next game is...
Who can eat a lot of mandarin oranges?
It's the third time, but you're out again like this
Game start!
Did it feel good?
White, red.
I told you it feels so good.
Red
Well then
Chance
Let me make you feel better
Shall we go to bed
Zero
Please!
I was surprised.
Go, go.
You want me to do more, don't you?
Because it is absolutely a secret
I think we can win this game
No way!
You never listen...
Pink team seems to be strong
Pink team is really strong
Let's announce the result
From 4th place
The fourth place goes to
Let's taste it!
You were surprised, right?
Chuu feels good
I can't do it anymore.
Please lie down on the bed
Then I'll do something more pleasant for you.
Okay, cut.
Can I eat this?
Go ahead and eat as much you want to
Lastly
Do you like your nipples?
If we can endure the amazing technique of an AV actress
We will be able live
You're very nervous, aren't you
Please go for it
Don' make a dump!
Girls, please show us your Sugoteku.
Would like me to lick your nipples too
Let me see your Sugoteku!
Okay
Let's lick a lot
I don't have a Sugoteko so...
Wow
You're getting better, aren't you?
You do have one though?
No
Yes
Wait a minute!
Don't do that
Ready set go
This is the last game
It's disgusting
It's me!
Stop it
Wait a minute.
I might have been in trouble when you were standing up straight
If you can bear with the amazing technique of an AV actress,
Wait, it's going to be on camera
Can we change the subject?
it is a live friendship.
It was so awkward that if you had said PIN
then it would have been on camera
Ready? Start
Like this
It really looks good
I'making it a secret.
You love your nipples, don't you?
I will not give it to you immediately because there are many people who have come
Here is the pose of Harlem.
Make sure you keep it from your mother!
If people see us like this they'll get embarrassed
Ready, go!
This is the play of Harlem by winning team!!
Let's make her feel good
The game will be over now
It's time for Harlems
I want more.
Your stomach is hard again
I'm Chiba
That's a bad way to say it
You got 70 points
Please sit on the chair
It got this big again
You can go back
Pants and glasses
Then let me stroke while licking the nappies
I'll lick you a lot.
A few minutes later
Masaki-san
What is Chichijyo
Chichijyo means
Mr Imori
I'm getting a lot of energy.
You are happy person, aren't you?
What should we do next...
Let's try to jump rope on the trampoline!
Ready, go!
My legs are short so it might be possible
Konnichiwa.
Do you want to take a bath?
Yes we do!!
It feels good
You're all sweaty now...
Really
Really?
Yes.
What's wrong?
But there are two types of hot water for men and women in the bathroom
You want me to lick your chin, don't you ?
One is hell and the other one is heaven
It's called a bath.
Please choose which one you want to take!
All right!
Let' s do it
I've decided on the place for you guys
Which way?
Amazing!
Let' go right away
3,2
Do you feel good in my mouth
I can bend my nipples
Can you do that now ?
It feels good.
It'so hot.
What?
No way
I'm in heaven.
Did not expect that
There's nothing here, right...
Touch my neck, too
Yeah!
Poor guys
Men don't get along with each other
I've never done this before but it feels so good
Are you guys coming?!
I wanna do it so bad
We've only done it once
Do you have any particular thing to show us
Or just a little bit of sexiness
Sexines-
Are we going again
You want me out
It's hard
Just now
Well
But I want to do it, because you did it with a hand-held machine earlier.
Do you want to bend over?
no
You're losing weight
No, I want to feel good too.
If that happens...
Can't you take off your clothes?
Hold on a little longer
You poor thing
Poor thing
There's only one person left
It'so good.
I'm sweating a lot, too!
It won' t be more than 9 years old
Please
Please do.
I'm glad that you are here with us today,
because we can't leave you alone
I feel great!
It feels great!!
or a beautiful actress like her behind
Look at this sweat...
What kind of friendship story is this?
My nose is running now...
Give me your nose water, please
It's good!
It's a good story.
Do you want to drink it?
So,
You are Yuta-san
You got a pimple on your nose.
I'll give you the job
I want to get rid of it soon!
Is it OK?
Even for me
Is it really okay to do this
Let three of us
Is it delicious, the pimple on your nose??
But there is one condition
You were going to say it again
Soda-chan's is also delicious!!
Because we are employees
We have an interview
Get more pimples!!!
Can
Of course
no
I can't do it.
Let's do it with three people
Please
Then make sensei feel better
I can't do it.
It is a woman
It's hard.
Do it more
Thank you
You look like the story of good men
There are many guys
I want you touch my butt
Do you like that?
Then, take off your microphone
Take off the microphone
Really
Are you sure?
If you lie to me, I'll be angry.
This is embarrassing
Here is my bag!
You can keep it here
She's lying
What's wrong with me?
Can we help her take off the clothes
Excuse us
Start
How is the teacher's underwear?
My back hurts!
Lift up
cute
Good
I'm not used to it yet.
You're going to get a cramp
So touch your body
Touch my neck.
Oh, my God.
Be gentle, okay?
My face is so blue
You want to put this on, right?
It was a good time with you?
Mori-san, do you know what did he say?
Do you know what it is?
Vivian
Can we take a picture of you wearing that one time
I don't know
It's a temanu
Really
Using this teman-kin
Anaru, do you want to try too
A little scary
Let me be gentle
Didn't she say something about being sexy
It feels good!
Here
There are people who are sexy
Tasty
The suction power is great
It's a bit erotic.
Isn't it?
Yuzawa-san, you are so funny!
I'm so full
Yeah
You made me sad...
I feel great.
He came back to us
He is poor
It feels good!
Dirty spirit
Let's get better together
If you squeeze a lot
Don' do that
My win
This pipe is very beautiful
You're still here?
Yes.
Go home!
Very beautiful
Okay, I'm sorry
There are so many types of bread.
Does it feel good?
This is the first time for me to have fun
It's like this...
Touch my neck too
It's the first time you've put it in your butt?
Yeah, I'm glad.
Wow!
He still has a lot of energy left
My butt feels so good
Mori-san was definitely perverted
Kurochan is pervert
I'm so tired.
Do you like your teacher's boobs ?
So this is where you were
Can you do me one more favor?
Sit down, please
Do you like my boobs?
Are you taking a day off because of your illness
Put it in here
Touch my nipples.
It is really beautiful!
Did they say that
you bullied the students in our class
What is this!
How could you bully my student?
How hard is thiis!?
You were bullying him, weren't you.
What's this?
A dog.
I'm going to eat it all up!
It looks like a chinko is growing in your mouth
It's no use hiding it from me
What the hell is thiis
Feels good but never seen anything like this
Tell us how
Don'tell anyone, okay
Looks more manly
What on earth
You're trying so hard
Does that feel good
Umi-san, I'm going to take a picture of this.
I don' want to see your face
Look up!
You were bullying me, weren't you?
Well...
I wont stop until you tell the truth.
It feels so good
It feels good
Hey, can you touch my tongue?
Does it feel good?
Im not going to let it go
See
Oh my god
Come closer
You should come closer
I'm so happy.
I'll push your back and do a lot of painful things for you
Oh, my God!
Next
Are you feeling good?
Here
How is it?
No, Chikubi...
Why not!?
Let me do it again
Is it painful for you to do so much pressure on me like that.
Can't you let go of something else
What's wrong with that
It feels good
OK
Can I eat it?
You can ask me not doing this anymore, but I won't stop even if someone asks
I'm going to do it.
Here we go!
It's nice, isn't it?
If I touch your tongue like that...
...you'll feel better.
Oh, no...
No good
Hey, touch me directly.
How about this one.
My heart is pounding
What kind do you like the most ?
Wow you did a lot
Do you want to be pushed more ?
Soy sauce
This is the best
Hey Mori-san
You can do more right?
I'll put it in for you.
Do you see it??
No, no...
It's embarrassing to look at you like that...
Put more in there!
More?
I'll put it between my disgusting crotch
You're going home tomorrow so be careful with that
It's all up to me
Yeah right
Feels good
How is it?
What do you think about this one, huh...?
Hmph...!
Wow
Do you like this one
Uuuhhhhh!!!!
Nnnnngggg.....
You can't breathe anymore now right!?
Do yo want me to massage more of your head??
Is it painful?
Hey, rub my belly too.
I love you, too!
Wow
Do you want me to rub it more?
Is the teacher's manko warm?
I'll rub it even harder.
I'm going to massage you a lot more than before.
Rub it more...
You're looking forward to it, aren't you?
Are you okay?
It's painful...
How is it now...?
Ouch!
I feel sick.
Oh, my God!
You're good at touching me.
Oh my gosh
Where do you want to go?
It'so hot
Muneo-san, open your mouth wide and say it out loud
Open my mouth
Can I lick you again?
Are you ready?
It's disgusting
I'm going to rub it with more towel.
It's a lot of rubbing...
Is it good now that the fever has gone down a little bit
Hey, do you want to put this silver towel in the teacher's room.
Are you still going to go out?
You can do it, right?!
It was so good just now.
Why are you running away from me??
How is it?
I have a pace...
Then i also have my own pace
Me too
Wait wait
Oh, no!
That was fast.
Masaki-san...
You didn't run away?
You rubbed me so much.
I have a good pace for this kind of thing
Me too
Is it painful?
It feels good, doesn't it ?
It felt so good
Did you get surprised by it
I'm happy for you
What's with the T shirt
No, you don't.
Whatever
Do you want me to do it for you?
Alright
Let me put on my tshirt
I'll take off your shoes
I've wanted this since we first met
It's no use even if we make a mess
Please keep it a secret
It is only between two of us
It's a secret.
You're so defenseless.
I'm going to kiss you now!
I'm going to bed.
Good night!
Do you want me...
What's wrong?
...to lick your lips?
What are you doing, Shishii-san?!
It feels so hard...
Wait a minute...
What is it today...?
You're not in the mood for this kind of thing...?
But it feels good because it is big and hard
Hold on...!
Shishiii san!!
We're working here right now
Don't leave me alone
Just wait
Wait just waiting
Your tits feel really good
Hey what arent we supposed do??
How is it?
I was able to do it.
Do you want me to do more for you
But you're not.
I'll embarrass you even more
What's your name?
Yamada-san
Yama
You're not
Sensei, my back won't stop
It was salty
You were late yesterday
I didn'take a bath
That explains it
Hey, can I move a lot?
Just be bright
It's getting really hard.
Look at the place where you are in.
Hey
You're over there...
Wait without licking me!
We played
Played
It's okay, but wait a minute!
Hello?
Thank you very much
I'm sorry, but you can't come in here anymore
You gave me a free service
I did
I haven't brushed my teeth yet...
Here.
It feels so good!
I'll feed you with my own hands
Do you want to lick?
Make it harder
Ah, it'so hot.
Chikubo?
Are you doing well now ?
Give me more.
Yes
It feels good!
My voice is coming out
Everyone is here
You're sweating
2,000 yen
It'sour.
Sour!
Wait, wait...
I can't do it anymore.
It'so hot!
What is it?
It was so good.
What?
Hey, what's going on here.
I didn't know that you are such a great actor, Erii-san!
Thank you for your cooperation next time as well
Which one do you feel better?
Give me the money!!
Are you OK now ?
No problem at all !
You're smiling a lot today
OK
No way
Please say something to the camera
Do both of them feel good to you ?
That's it
So, this time you move
Let me do it again
It is too spicy for me to eat this alone
but
I'll try my best
and
enjoy the rest of the video
Bye-bye
Oh, no
Pass this over
Interview...
Here?
Ama-san, you're amazing.
Please give us an interview
You can hold it in so well!
I'm working but my stomach is full...
It's hard to drink.
It's too much right?
Yeah because of work and we haven't even gone home yet
What are you doing!?
Look at me
I'm going to do it.
Hold this.
You've been doing this for a while, haven't you?
Be quiet!
Thank you for your hard work!
You are slimy now...
Can I lick your throat?
How should we react when they see us like this...
We did it without thinking much of the situation
This feels good
Has the meeting started yet?!
Yes
It's open
It'so hot.
Really!?
Oh really!!
Are there any questions left??
There are still some
I'm going to work now.
Thank you for your hard work!
You like rubbing your butt, don't you?
She is working so hard!!
Aren't you tired?
No, thank you very much
You were taking a rest
It's getting really hard.
We had sex over there
You have a lot of bacteria, Hana-chan
What!?
Good job
Let's watch the interview and do our work
Do you know that?!
It's amazing
I feel like my stomach is going to explode...
Yes
No idea
I'm not good at English.
Here...
Do you want me to rub here too?!
I'll do it for you!
I can't lick it.
Lick it!
It's painful...
Look at me.
Is this a job?
Oh, it feels good!
Wait, wait
Everything is dirty
I'll take it off for you.
No, no...
Don't be sorry!
You're going to lose a lot of hair on your head
It'summer now
Oh yeah?
Your head is shaking
I'm so tired.
Are you okay?
My neck hurts
The room behind is very expensive, but...
You're naked!
It's Yoripi-dori.
This is embarrassing
Does it suit me well
I can't do it anymore.
It suits you
Let's go to the actual shooting.
Ready, start!
Let me see a girl first
I'm not ready yet
I'm going to sleep.
She is about that old lady
Wait, wait!
Please ask her
This is my first time
Really?
Ask the girl directly
If you do that again...
Do it
I'm waiting for you to do it.
You're going out?
You should look at the audience more
Because your eyes are out of focus now
What's that in your hand
What's that?
Brother!
Wait a minute.
Come here
Look at him
What is this!
Don't do it
It is embarrassing
He is kind
You are stupid
Brother, he is kind
You're a toilet idiot.
Stop it!
There are a lot of people.
Let's go to the next one!
Don't make that weird face...
Are you ready?
Yes, let' s go
Do we have enough tickets for this time too!?
We only have 20 thousand yen
I like this kind of smell, you know?
OK
I'm ready
Seriously?!
Which one do you want me take with us
Which is it
It's not funny at all
You mean which way
Right
What should we do?
This way
This
How about this girl
That was intense
That girl
Is that okay
Wait
Sure
Do you want me to take it off for you
Wait
She said yes
Yay
This is crazy!
Really
It's okay.
We have to get comfortable on our own, right?!
Let's go, let' go
I want to do it while looking at the sky
I have more money than you do, though...
What are you talking about?
You've got a lot of money now!
Wait a minute
This is the only way to win this game
I love you.
She has 50%
I happen to have a room that my aunt used.
Let's go together!
Feels good
Go with me, please
Please
Go with her
Thank you
Excuse us
Did you enjoy?
Oh, you were about to sleep?
Thanks
Not yet.
It'so comfortable
You were about to sleep!
She is waiting for the staff
Yes I was...
I'm waiting for you to sign it.
It's like the spirit is in my throat
Maybe just below
Please go inside the room and take a look at her.
Can we see it
No no
Please come inside the room and take care of me, please
What is that
Close your back
Aren't you sweating
You have no face
Yeah
Close your back
Are you okay?
I'll be right there.
Thank you very much!
It'stuck in my chest...
Nice to meet you, too
Me too
Sorry that we are not actresses
You're making my head spin.
It's cute, isn't it?
No problem
Really!
This one is better
It's good
I'm happy. Thank you very much
Are you inexperienced?
No, not at all
Have you ever seen a shy girl before
I can't get up.
Yes
You are
Do you like it?
I've been curious about this since the morning.
Oh, it feels good!
You're like an old lady, right now
Sorry for being weird
The eyes are in a good place
It doesn' t usually happen to men
Would you touch it
Oh, it feels so good.
It feels so good...
Oh really
That's how men are.
It's perfect
No way!!
I didn't know that...
I think that's what they're aiming for.
They can attack you while saying,
Oh, no!
No way!!!
crush your eyes!
What should we do?
It looks like Osaka too
No way you're going to eat it all at once like that?
You can do whatever you want
We have to go home now
Your skin is so beautiful
Mine is also a bit pale
You'll break into pieces if you do so
Really
White and beautiful
It's good to be wearing a mask, isn't it?
What are you doing?
Well...I'm embarrassed now because of my job and doing something bad at the same time
You're taking it off.
Wait a minute!
It feels so good!
Kato Momoka-san
Yes
It's too hot...
Satou-san
She is working in this company
It's hot.
I feel good!
Right
Excuse me
Okay.
Wait, wait
I'm getting excited!
To think that it's me in the picture...
It's hot!
No, no.
It really is very white, isn't it?
What?
I couldn't hold it anymore.
I don't know what you're talking about anymore
Wait a minute
It's really warm now, isn' it?
Did you feel good?
Ouch!
Your nipple looks bad.
I don't know what to do with my body.
Do you want to see my boobs?
Do you want to see my hand?
Hey, can you still do it ?
What's wrong?
I want to try a little more.
You just want to live, right ?
Yes...
Can we try one more time
But it is not good enough for me anymore
Just look, don'touch.
Not good enough...?
But you said you wanted to go.
Your lips are soft and pleasant to look at
I want, but...
Like this?
What is it?!
Something's hitting me!
What are they hitting with!?
That makes me happy
I'm going to make it a lot harder.
It's just been out and it is still very hard
I don't know what's going on.
Does it feel good?
Don'tell your mom.
It feels good, but is there something bad hitting me now ?
Maybe
Wait a minute
Please don' tell your mom, okay?
Ouch!
No no
Did you feel good
Did it hurt?
It felt so good.
I feel like something bad is going to happen
Soda-chan, this is not good
Your dick is so nice that I want to have a lot of sex with it
The doctor wants you to go home
I'm so happy.
Oh no, I'm going to go.
Ugh
Can't we take thi...this off
Ahh oh my gosh
Is that okay
Oh, no.
I'm in trouble now!
You're also leaving?
Then next time
show me where you'll be leaving
It feels good, doesn't it?
Does it feel good to you ?
That makes me happy
No way...
Don't apply it on me!!
Please make me more comfortable
You'll make me angry if you do so
Yes
No, you can't apply it.
Why?
You shouldn' t do that!
It's disgusting...
I have to take responsibility for this mess
Oh my god
It feels so good
Don''t get married
But i'm not single
That would be a waste
Please make my feeling better
There is no need for recycling
You don't have to do that.
Does it feel good
Really
It'so hot.
Oh yes
Does it feel good?
Are you ready to go?
Take a deep breath.
Your finger...
Your penis is very thin
Don' interrupt my photo session!
I'll go all the way in there
You're out of breath now!
It's itchy.
Did it feel good for you today ?
I'm going to lick you.
If your parents aren't home, I'll tell them by the end-of month period
What are you doing?
You can also lick my chinchin
Ouch!
It's a little ticklish, isn't it?
First thing first...
Let's take bath since we've been sweating so much
Don' worry about it
Do you want me to cut this side of your hair
It feels good
I changed my clothes, how do you like it?
Oh no!
You look fine
Do you look good in it ?
Does it feel good?
What do you like being done
Is this cute??
I want a lot of food
Wait a second...
You are staring at me.
Ah, wait!
A lot
Are you still looking forward to seeing a sexy face again???
Oh, it's hot.
Wait...!
Even though we put out so many pictures just now...
...are your feelings still about being sexy?!
I can't do this anymore...
It feels good!
Because of the fact that he is really handsome!
It goes all the way to here...
It feels good.
Ah~~
He's touching his penis again
You haven't studied at all yet.
Please hold on tight
Then, look at me and tickle your belly button!
Let's feel good together
I'm going to do my best.
Hang in there!
Does it feel good?
Thank you for the meal
I can't breathe.
I'm going to do it alone so you can also tickle yourself
Wait a minute
I want you to take off more clothes.
Why?
You took them off twice, didn't you!
Let's do it again
Then cheer up a little bit more...
Wait wait Ebo-chan!!
Shut it!!!
We're not listening
Show me your hand
Excuse me
Good morning
What did we talk about today
Yes yes
It's comfortable, isn't it?
S or M
What's your name?
I'm M.
He looks very close
Let me see your face.
Do you like to dance ?
You can laugh now
Oh, yes!
This is what i brought with me
I'm going to beat you up.
What do you mean by that
Isn'this hard?
Please look at it
How
Yes, that's right.
More!
Show me more of your squinting face
Get stronger!
Like this?
It feels good.
When I look at you with a happy expression,
Sensei gets excited
Is it okay to do like this now?!
Show us more
I'll give you a little bit of shiko-shiko.
Like this?
Did you finish beating me all of them off ?
What do you want to do with this
You still have some on your nose
Poo
I'll poo, please don't
I can't run away.
This one
Doesn' it hurt
It's okay
You've been beaten up
Hey, is it working?
Yes.
The teacher went ahead...
Next time...
San-chan!
This time, the teacher will do it for you!
Where are you going?!
I'm going to wash your face.
Let's go.
I'll put it on you now
Ready, set...
Wow!
I can't forgive you if you bully me anymore.
Where are you going?
Now, do you understand?
You were shiko-shiko properly, weren't you?
Here it is
It's bigger than before!
You feel a lot of things, and that makes me happy
Bite me more.
Bite me some more!
So...
Are there any other students who bullied your behavior in the classroom ?
Is it comfortable to be Shiko in hot water ?
No
What should I do?
Just say it.
If you don't, we won' t go home
That was good
Do you like cleaning?
Well...
Tell me or not tell me
Yes
You're a pervert, aren't you?
Which one is better
Then let me do something more pleasant
Well
My nipples are so itchy...
Your nipples aren' itchy now that I'm holding them up for you
Do you know why people bully themselves
Let's put this in
Let my back float
Do you know what it is?
It'so cold.
I don't know.
Is it?
Then, let me tell you frankly
Does it feel good there, too
Have you ever seen yourself in the mirror
You're a poor man
I can't feel anything
How disgusting
And
Indifference to decision-making
It's pretty gross
Does it feel good to be licked on the belly?
What's going on?
I think it's the reason why you're being bullied these days.
My ears are all torn up.
You want to cut them?
Please help me!
Is that so?
Have you become brave now ?
What about this one here...
I may better at being a pervert than studying.
Well, yes...
Are you still hesitating about it !
It feels good, doesn't it?!
More more!!
Here.
Who are protecting whom with all those hesitations in your mind
Do like to be bullied
I want to go home.
Well, I'm not that weak.
What's wrong?
Then the situation won't change no matter how long you stand there!
Make your belly harder with my mouth
My father...
How is it?
Where are you hitting now ?
You're a pervert!
I'm hitting there!
Are you scared of being stepped on by my heels?!
You're scared aren´t you!?
So let'step on them with all our strength!!
My buttocks...
If we don' say anything quickly they'll really step in!!!
Really.
My heel is hitting your balls, isn't it?
Come here
Here
Hey, hey.
You look like you're in pain...
What did you say?
Do you like being born with a face that looks painful to me ?
I can't hear you
Even such perverted things can make people feel uncomfortable
I can't do it anymore.
Well then
If you don't want to say it, I'll make you do that.
I'm done, I've had enough!
You're so annoying...
What?
Take off this belt for me
Hey hey stop that
A lot came out
Really, it hurts so much
Belt...
You couldn't stand it
Hurry up
But it feels good
And take off the jacket
But I'm still standing.
I'm so happy.
The jacket
I see.
It's hot!
Next,
How do you feel?
put your pants down
What are you doing?
Hurry up!
You can't be satisfied with just one bath, right ?
OK
I don't know what you're talking about, but it's a good idea.
You can do that for me
Then...I'll give you more time to stand up!
Hey
It was just an accident
It smells so bad!
What's wrong with you
Are you excited because of being stepped on a little bit
Don't worry, I'll make you feel better too
Did you?
No, I didn't.
Eat it properly
If you don' t want to be embarrassed like this...
...say it quickly!
It's good
But that's…
Otherwise we'll do more perverted things for you
Do You like being stepped on by a gold ball
Do you like gold balls?
You stepped on my foot and made me hurt.
It was just a little bit...
It was painful to be bullied, wasn't it ?
Thank you very much
If there is someone who has been bullied by others
Thank you
please tell me the person who did that
It'so delicious!
I'm going to take off the rubber band.
There's a lot of sexual juice coming out from the tip
Does it hurt?
It's okay
Well...
Why are you covering your face?
You're right, it is really good...
Can you let me go out of your arms, please
You're looking at my underwear, aren't you?!
No... I'm not.
Thank you
So have you become a little brave now!?
It's disgusting!
Well....
Don' t make me beat up your dick! Say it quickly!!
Let me wipe your mouth a little bit more
No, I'm fine.
You're burning up!
Thank you so much
You're welcome
I can't believe it.
Do you want to see more?
It hurts a lot more than before, doesn'it?
Really?!
Yeah...
That was a healing sex
Ouch!!
These are your pants...
Are you cute now
I'm glad you felt that way.
How did you feel?
It was very pleasant
It doesn' matter how many times
Do you want to try it?
How do you feel now...?
Eat it properly.
Wow.
Did it hurt on the way there or not at all
Amazing!
No, it didn't
Your legs are getting numb and your heart rate is increasing rapidly...
Isn' t is tight
Is this better?
Come on, tell me what's wrong with you now
I can't
If you don' t say it out loud it will get worse
Thank you so much
Thank you for your hard work.
Oh, no.
I'll feel better.
I can't do it anymore!
Which one do you like, Ame-chan?
But
I'll take the purple one
Please forgive me.
Let's get better together!
What's wrong?
Are you not going to say it yet?
I'm so happy
It hurts so much...
Please help me out of this pain...!
Is it sweet
Oh, my God!
I can't do it anymore.
Thank you very much today
See him off
You're a big guy...
Uhhh
It's too painful!
Uh-huh
Please enjoy yourself again
Uhh
If you want to see my underwear that badly
Thanks
Thank you very much. I'll come back again
Yeah
I'll rub it on for you
Thank you
No
Rubbing
You're a pervert, aren't ya
It was really good
Nah
That's not what it is
How do you feel?
Do we go to the next one
Let'see
Ouch, my back hurts...
But there may be no more
Wow, there are so many pimples again
Thanks
Please tell me
Is this place okay?
You want me to do it harder?
It felt so good
It's open now.
I'm glad.
It'so hot.
I'm coming in!
No...
Does it feel good?
Yes, I do!
More more...
Does it feel good now??
The next customer is here, so let me give you a service right away
Come on.
Thank you
Can we buy half and half of the food
It's okay, you can stop now
Come on, say it.
You can go now.
The customers are waiting for you, so please hurry up and come in!
Are you feeling better?
You want to beaten hard?
I'm wearing a rubber band around my neck but it's okay?
Please
I'm going to beat you so hard that...
Let'study together again!
Are you okay?
...you don't want your face in the mirror anymore
This is definitely a secret, okay?!
Does it feel good like this, right here...
Are you okay with this?
Ah, it feels good.
Don' t do this
How do you feel now??
It's really bad...
Oh my god!
Show me your face!!
Does it hurt a lot ?
It hurts so much
Why are you hiding it from us!?
How does that feel
You're getting more and more intense.
Feels great
Here
Come on show us!!!
I put in lots of juice
You'really feeling it, aren't you?
It'll be easier if you tell me, so hurry up and say it!
Okay
We'll clean your ears when the bath is over
Do you feel like this when I cut your hair.
You're always writing about sex.
It feels good
Who was bullying you?
Did you listen to your teacher's class?
Come on now...
Don'tell me that you can no longer concentrate on studying because of the dizziness again
Which part do you like best
Faster
What?
This one
Yeah
There.
Can I let it go?
Go ahead
That's Minami-sensei.
It's big
Senseei?!
Yes, yes
Sensei is...?
I'm going to die
Wow
Then I'll make it clear for you
Oh, my God.
He's very nervous
What do you like to be done
Instead,
Do you like being licked
Is there anyone else?
It seems like your patience is not enough
I got it.
No one...
Did you get it?
It seems like you're not good at it, so please be patient until the teacher says yes.
Here you are!
Does it feel good here
Here
See?
Feels good
Is this
Can you promise?
How is it?
It's much better now!
Good boy...
It feels good, doesn't'it!?
Oh my god..
You are sweating a lot.
Your gums are hard.
Did you get hurt?
Then sit on the sofa and show me your penis quickly
I can't do anything.
Let me see your hand
Don't push yourself too hard!
It'so big!
Can I put this in your mouth now, please
Let me apply some ointment
Stop it!
What kind of posture do you like the most
The best one
Did you remember something erotic and were in a daze
Me too
I'm going to clean your ears.
Okay, let'start cleaning your ears!
Do I want to put it back into your pussy again
Oh, my God.
Do you think so?
What?
I'm in trouble...
You are in trouble...?
Yes
What's wrong with you?!
You are already sexy.
What's wrong?
It hurts so much!
Then, I'll stroke your hair with my hands
It is getting harder and harder!
It's okay.
Maybe it will be fine
I can't breathe.
Please put the cotton swab in my ear
Me, too
Wow!
Put it in
Yes
It's getting harder and harder
Let's take a break
Let me give you a high-speed syringe now
Does this hurt?
Is it that good to be stroked by a teacher
Ouch!
Can you bear it?
Okay, okay
It'so hot.
It hurts
Does it feel good?
It's very narrow.
Yes, it does!
Oh my god...
Which do you like better slow or fast
Oh, my hands are sticky.
I'm so tired...
This is crazy
I couldn't bear it anymore and took them out of the closet
10 more seconds
Wow!
Well then
Let me try slowly
9, 10...
The floor is dirty
It's not a big deal
11.
It's really disgusting, so it is natural to be bullied by this
Sorry
Can you make it clean?
You've grown up again.
Cleanly
You're going to break it.
Yes
What is it?
Do you want some water, too...?
Hang in there!
My stomach hurts!
Please give me a lot of water...!
I love your poop, too!
Hold on a little longer...
Oh my gosh!!
You can go home now
It feels so good
Is it OK if I crush your head?
What?
Wow!
Yes, please do so
Yes
But you can't let it out on your own
It's going down
It hurts.
Thank you.
More, more...
Let's make it a little faster
Can you do it?
I can't anymore!
Hold on a second
Do you feel good?
It's hurting
Are you going to go away
No
Why are you crying?
I feel sick.
It's amazing
No.
It hurts, it hurts...
You can't do this anymore!
Can I touch your feet?
I told you, right?
It hurts so much
You don't have enough patience
But that's okay
Then
Please hold on
Can i go now
Go on
Let's do it while looking at the teacher
You can do it.
You want to go, don't you?
I'm going!
Hurry up and get in there
That way you can see it closely
Oh no...
Ecchi
You can do it.
It'still coming out, right?
Go on!
Can you stand this
Amazing...
More more
You're back.
Did you feel better?
Yes, I did
It sounds ecchi
Did it hurt a lot ?
can hear
Sorry, it was a little early
No
Excuse me
Are we going to go again
It's dirty so let me clean it
Is that so?
What about your lungs
They are fine
Let's change your clothes
Let him clean them
It doesn't hurt, does it?
No.
Open your mouth
Thank you so much
But you were able to endure it properly, right
Come in
How was the surgery today
It went well
Me too
How is it?
Ms Ushio
Is it good??
What is it
I'm glad you're okay.
Do you want more???
Then I'll count 10 again
You can add when it becomes zero
You were bullying the students, weren't you?
Isn't it tight?
Donít you think itís cowardly for a teacher to bully his students.
More!?
You are amazing!
Let's go
Are you ready
You were hiding and secretly bullying them
I want more.
Thank you for your hard work today!
Ten
Do you know how much this punishment is heavy
Oh, thank God...
Nine
It's raining a lot
Thank you very much
You are so weird.
I want more!
Please enjoy yourself
Eight
Can I wear all of these
What do you mean?
More?
Thanks
Seven
Good morning.
It's an introduction practice for a teacher to teach students.
She wants more, give her some more
Six
Are you crazy?!
Are you okay??
This punishment is heavy, isn't it
I don' t know if Ms Yoshida will accept this
Give me
Shut up
You can shut up but please take the punishment
How is it Shira
It's a little embarrassing
Thank you for your hard work today!
Look she wants something else
I'm sorry to wake you up before going back home, because we have a lot of work tomorrow as well
Is that okay with you
Punishment
I've endured half of it, so
How was it working with AD?
I'm so happy.
Instead of teaching students
Let me show you my boobs as a reward.
It's a little embarrassing for me to say this, but...
What are you doing?
This is great!!
It was harder than what imagined
You're too perverted
I'll punish you for your embarrassment.
Please don'teacher!
We didn't know how and where should move
Don't follow me
And there were so many people
You want me to shut up right!?
Then be quiet and accept my punishment
This is the second time I've done it.
The actress was amazing!
You look like you're going to live
She overpowered me and made me cry
Being punished like this...
How do you feel about today?
But,I'll do my best
It's embarrassing
Yes
More than today
Is it done yet??
No no
Please prepare for tomorrow
Yes it is
More???
Embarrassing isn'it
We haven' done it yeat
The students must have been ashamed of you, too.
I'm having a hard time with the technology.
Thank you
No...
They were disgusted with you and…
What are you doing?
Good night
Good night.
He's trying to do it!
It's their fault!
Their fault?
Stop it like this!!
What do they mean by that?!
I'm just trying to calm them down a bit…
The next day
Shall we have some competition!?
What kind of competition is that??
Please don't go on like this
Just a little more
You might hear me talking, but there are actors in the Japanese-style room
I'm going to do my best.
You're weak because
That's what we're doing now, right?
Have you ever seen Tomaki before???
it was me who bullied you
No, no...
No
Is this your first time seeing her?!
Be prepared.
Thanks to you guys!
Please don't do that!
Yeah
I'm the only one who'scared of it.
Great
What is the name of this dance in the play?
If you can get through 10 minutes, we'll give you a lot more money
That part is a bit…
You flew a lot.
A bit what?
Do you feel this part of your body?
Panko
Really?
It was just ten minutes
Don' t be so embarrassing
But you were patient and great!
That was easy
Here it goes
I thought it was over
You can do it
Because my hair has been damaged
Ready, action!
Did this give you some endurance?
Let'start the Dynamico.
What are you doing to me teacher!?
Well then
Yo
Start!
You should have been hit with your left hand more often, Mr. Yaisabe
Well, I'll do more erotic things for you because it's hard work
Please stop
It's important to receive the punishment
It's Hana-chan.
Wow, you're so cool
Stretch your legs
What?
Is it okay to do this here
You don't want me to come in
I'm not that drunk
There are people crying over there
If you don't stand up for shooting
Wait wait
Can I help you?
Wait
Is it painful?
With my hand
You cry because it doesn' turn into a work
Wait a minute.
It is your job to do that
It's been 10 minutes!
Let's help her.
I'm so tired.
Can I do it?
Hold on, hold on...
What are we going to be doing
You can't do it, right?
Let me do it
I'm gonna lick your favorite nipples
I'll lick you.
9 minutes
It's not over yet!
Wait, wait.
I'll start with the warm one.
Three of you!
Ah, it'so hot!
He's not alone
I was told not to participate in this game, but...
Look at him
Stop it!!
What?
There are three of us
Touch me!
It is OK to take it out?
Show it to me
You can be more excited
It'so hard.
How do you feel?
I feel like my breath is being taken away from me...
Do you feel good now ?
It'so good.
I'm feeling great.
Don't you have any pain in your body anymore
No, it's fine
Are you getting excited, Jinpo?
I'm looking forward to it.
Ouch!
Let me look at you more closely
You've grown up again after licking your nipples!
Do your best alone!
You pervert.
Wait, wait
Wait a minute
There are a lot of guys, so you can't have fun with all the users?
Oh, it's delicious.
You are so fluffy
How about this?
Girls will never be enough for sure
Can you mix in some more girls
What do you mean by that
I almost made you suffocate
I don't know, so it's not good to stop the user and go home.
Are you excited?
It is a last scene after all
It is a little spicy
So you can take off your skin here
Thank you very much.
You're wearing a very embarrassing outfit, aren't you
I'll take a look at your embarrassing back, Sensei!
That is also as work
You are happy with that
Wow! Delicious
The user will be happy
Then give this
Can you hold thiis?
You just have to listen to me quietly and don't say anything else
Go where the overflowing man
Let's go to the man and say, I'll help you.
Thank you.
This is the best!
Your face is so round
Where are you going?
It's embarrassing, doctor.
The person just now is out of breath so let him come here
I can see your embarrassing lower body clearly now
Good luck
It's delicious
Embarrassing?
I'm not good at swiss hock
Okay let' get in
Do you see anyone waiting for the guy
You like being pushed like this
You like it, don't you?
Oh, it feels so good
There he is
Sit down.
It feels so good.
My boobs...
I'll do anything for you
Your temperature is rising.
Are you enjoying?
Oh, it feels great!
I went away immediately
It really does feel great
Let me see
I'm not the only one who feels good about this...
Did you go away immediately
Please make me feel good too!
This is awesome
It's a little hard.
Let's enjoy again
We have time until the end
I'm getting used to it
It doesn't hurt
Can't we put our fingers in?
Wait a minute
Don't do that.
Get up
Let me lick you!
Oh, there's a mango in your mouth...
Can you let it out?
Oh, my God.
I want to eat it first
Hurry up.
Hey...
This is the last one.
You're crying from behind?
You're wearing such an embarrassing outfit, but you pooped a lot again
Five minutes have passed!
Can you hurry up a bit, please
Thank you very much!
Then let me make your mouth feel better
I think he's happy to see you again
I don't have anything yet
I want you to hurry up.
You're making me nervous, Chimpo.
It'so heavy!!
Hurry up!
I want to take revenge on him...
Pervert!
I'm really a pervert and you make me so nervous...
No, no...
Oh, he came back!!!
Go on already!!
This is the last time we do this kind of thing
I'll make you happy
and embarrassed
Let me out
Why are you laughing?
What are you doing?
Do you want a revenge on me??
It's almost August
Hurry up.
No way....
Sora-chan, please answer the phone!
Oh, sorry
Your hair is all messed up
It'so hot!
Yeah
Hehe
Hehehe
It's delicious
You put a lot of soup stock in it!
It'salty
Hey
Do you want the doctor to do it too?
Hurry up
Let's lick each other.
Do you want to feel good about the teacher?
Lick? What are you talking about!
Do you want to join?
I'm not in the mood for that right now
Wait a minute
You're so persistent with my punishment.
Can I join in the video too??
Hurry up and let me out
I want touch it.
Hey,
Sensei, can you do it for me?
How is it?
What is it now
Can you not do it?
Do you want more
Hey, touch your boobs.
Please!
No no
I'm doing my best.
Great!
You're getting better
More?
Sensei
I'm suffocating.
It's hard
Let's do it seriously
How long are we going to keep doing this
It'so good!
Sense
Didn't you say that my footwork was too much
I'm getting bigger.
We won'r be able get out of here
You are bigger than before, aren't you?
It gets harder
Wait
It feels good
Not yet
Yes
This is the end of your lesson, right?
Hey, not yet
Can we go down again
Sure
Wow
What are you doing here!
Feels great
It'so hot.
I want to take a nap...
Be quiet, be quiet!
You're very good at touching it
You can't run away from me
Let me get you some water too
It'so hot.
There's no way to escape
You won't be punished, will you?
Sorry, what did you say?
I'll make sure to punish you.
It feels so good!!
Punish me...?
Oh my god...
Feels great!!!
My punishment...
I put a manko in my boobs
It's rubbing against your skin
I want to take a bath here!
Oh my god!
Wait, it tickles me...
Touch your manko
It feels so good.
No way!!
It really tickles!!!
Wow
You're tickling me. I can't do anything, so stop it!
Sorry...
You're tickling!!
How do you feel?
Don''t laugh at him
You seem to be in pain
I feel so good!
Stop iiitttt!!!
Stop it
Aren't you ashamed of yourself
But this is not what a student should be ashamed of, is it?
What are you doing?
Wipe off your tears
I'm going to eat you.
A student shouldn't be like that...
You have to take the punishment seriously!
Wait a minute!
Come on, come here
This will make me feel better
Why?
It tickles
How do you feel now
Wait
No
Does it feel good?
Baby, you are going to die!!
Uh-huh.
It's dangerous, isn't it?
Yeah
Umm
Hurry up!
Oh, my God.
You're too forceful.
You are getting harder and harder!
It's funny, isn't it?
Wait a minute
Don't say that...
Do you like to beaten up so much?
Stop it
I think it's a good thing for me
I feel so good.
You want to take out the scab
It feels so good!
Oppa, it feels great
I'll do that
Let'stay here
So I want to kiss you again.
Put your chin on the floor
You want to take it out, right?
I might do that.
I'm so tired.
Hey, put your finger in the mango...
Your boobs!?
Here we go!
It's warm...
Wow
That is a lot
It flew away
But you want me too
Excuse me, this is...
Then let us leave
It's amazing.
What?
It's not over yet!
I'm scared.
This is my feeling
Calm down
Wow!
Are you okay?
You are great, aren't you!?
It'so hot!
Do you want to get out of bed now??
No...
What is that face for???
Me too!!
I feel so good!!!
Oh my god..
Why?
It's all my fault...
Feels good
Looks like he feels good
Don't ever touch Seika again, okay?!
Did you call me...?
How do you feel now ?
Inside...
Thank you very much !
You can do it.
Help me, please!
I can't do it.
It'so big!
It'so hard to breathe...
I'll put your kiss in it.
I got it.
You got two of them at once?
Yes, that was great
I'm going to die...
It's coming, it is coming!
Yeah you did
Thanks to me
Thank you
That felt so good
I'm so tired.
It's time to die!
It gets bigger as you put in more
Where are you going?
Please hold this
I'll punish you.
Take this!
Are you always like this?
It feels good.
We have 10 minutes left, right!?
Let us play a punishment game!!
Please put it in again
What is it??
Do that thing for me
Why???
Seriously
Put your spirit into the bean bag
It's nothing serious...
Wow
It's hard and big
You look happy
Feels good
Excuse me?
That part feels good
It's a waste of money, so...
I want more
Wait!
I can't breathe.
You did it, you did it!!
Don't you feel sorry for it?!
You're doing great
I'm scared!
Because it is small
Do you feel good?
Yes, it's great!
Why are you apologizing to her
What did she say
Don't pull it out.
I can not pull it out
It is very hard...
Sorry for everything
Please stop
Sorry that you can no longer do properly
He's gone already.
Sensei, it still isn't enough?
Oh, wait a minute
Wait
Are you okay?
You're under the bed
Since you're moving
Is it too weak for you, Chikuwa-san
Oh, it hurts.
I'm sorry for being late.
Wait a minute!
Why are you opening your legs?
can we do more of this exercise for you to see how much longer it takes
It's gone again...
You're going further and further away, aren't you?!
I'm glad you're feeling better now!
Do you want to go with me now??
What is it that's bothering her so much???
Hey...
Why am l getting bullied by my sister-in law!?
Why do they bully us like this!!
Even though he has been doing this so many times
Oh no!!!
It feels really hard
Oh, no.
You've got a lot of blood on your face
You don' feel good at all
Don't be so close to me
Oh, no.
No...
Sensei, your gait is so comfortable.
Wait a minute!
He might bite the window
I can't do it properly, sorry.
Let's get more comfortable together!
Who is that?
Ah...feels good
What is this?!
Hello
See you later
It'so hot.
Wait a minute
Take a break.
Stop it!
Hey, can I do it from the back?
You look good.
Just a little bit...
Good job today
Is your boyfriend not here?
He's not here
It's getting better
How do you feel?
Do you still want to do this again
I'm feeling great!
Can we put it in your mouth now!?
I can see your muscles
It feels good, doesn't it?!
Excuse me.
May I come in?
Yes, of course
Can you take a picture for me
I want you to do it more.
Of course
What's going on here
You don't have to do it yet
It feels good, doesn't it?
That is the plan
Just one more time.
But...
Is that so?
It doesn' matter
Oh no! Someone just came
Ouch!
What?
Do you feel pain here, Chiru-san
I'm not good at that
You don't know
You're a man
Yanase-chan, it's over!
My back hurts because I'm in a good mood.
Because of your sensitivity
That's great
It is over...
What are you complaining about?!
I'm not done yet...!
You're not done yeet!! We have to clean up afterwards!!!
It'so hot.
Don't look so dissatisfied.
Does it feel good?
Clean up the mess, quickly!
Yes, but if someone comes I'll get mad...
You don' t have to look so displeased
Can't sleep
Thank you very much
You don' t play games anymore
Let's go
No
Thanks
But
I'll do more for you.
It's really bad...
It hurts so much!!
Satsuki, come here.
Oh, yeah!
This is a little bit....
Did you turn on the switch?
What?
I was having fun at last but it's over now...
Wait wait
Are you OK with this??
So that makes me want to have more fun by myself!
Hey, can you move too?
Let me help you
It is a rule after all
The next day
I'm going to get you.
I'm gonna give him a massage now
Wait, wait!
Are we doing this again!?
You...
Hey
Calm down
Finally
Let's do it in pairs! 6-2,6
It's not over yet, Sensei.
We're going up
Yama-chan
What?
Everyone did you have fun?
What are you doing?
I didn't do anything wrong, did it?!
No no. Read the air!
No way...I can not read the air
How much is fine
Good job
You're in my way
Don' help me
Help...?
Don''s run away
Why why
Please help
Not so clearly
Stop it
I'm going to do it.
What are you doing, Yama-chan?
Excuse me for disturbing you...
This is strange!
It'so hot.
I feel sick...
Yama chan
What are you really doing
It's getting cold...
Let me hug you!
Thank you for your hard work.
Is it heavy?
You were the last one to go through a rough time, how was it?
Yes, a lot of food is in my mouth now
There are so many people like this in the crowd and I felt really embarrassed
What's wrong?
How do you feel?
It's hard.
It was my first time but
It's getting harder and harder.
Even though were nervous
I feel good!
I was happy, but at the end it made me want him to feel better.
I'm starting to feel better, aren't you?
Uhhh
Uh
You'really energetic!
Sometimes it is too much...
Uhh
What are you talking about?!
You looked like you wanted to be in a good mood and that's not what happened?
No way!!
Usually i don' t do this kind of thing
I'm not going to do it.
No no! It was just my wish for him
If you pull out your skin, you will be fine
Because he is an employee
Yes because of that
So from now on too
We will do our best
I'll do my best.
Your skin is beautiful when pulled out
This is the end of today'shooting, so thank you for your hard work!
Thank you very much
There's nothing we can't help
Good luck with your training
Oh, my God!
Thank you
Thank You
Wow, you're making a lot of noise again
Did it feel good?
It is over
Thank you.
Awesome
[created using whisperjav 0.7]
Hey
Until the last drop
Take out everything
Are you OK?
I'm not sure if it's a panty or what, but you were wearing something.
Oh, my God!
It was there...
It'still this hard
You're right!
Can I lick it?
Do as you like.
A little more.
I'll hold it with water for a while
How do you feel?
It feels so good
Wow, it'so cold.
Are you ready to go out with me ?
If I make you more aggressive...
Okay, let's take a lot of rice.
...will you feel better?
It hurts!
Kenji!
Oh, my God!
Wow!
You're amazing!
You took all the rice out for us !
Are you sure about that, Haru-chan?!
Do you feel better now that we have taken so much rice out for us ?!
I'll make you feel better.
Really?
You're a big boy now, aren't you?
But...
Didn'you see the movie last night ?
Yes
Was it good movie
No
Ta-dah !!
This is omurice made by my teacher
It's okay to get up slowly.
It looks delicious doesn't it?!
Well then I'll start eating right away
I'm tired...
The bear is crying
If you don't eat a lot, you won' t be able to study.
It's different from what I saw in the park.
You didn't see it earlier, did you?
You have no choice but bite it properly
You've been holding it in for so long.
How is it? Is delicious
I know you want to do more, but you can't stand it anymore?
Let me help you feel better
What are you doing over there ?
He eats very deliciously
There is something like a crunching sound
Maybe it hits deep inside
I'm going to fall!
I'm happy
I understand.
Eat another mouth
Eat it, Naan.
Stick it on the bed.
Rub more
Is it weak?
Yes, it is
How do you feel now Chikkun
Why are you doing that
You're watching again?
Please, teacher.
Even though you were eating
Did you do something else again
If you promise me not to hurt the students again...
I can make it a secret for myself as well
Can you promise?
I can't help it
Yes
Because if you hurt my cute students
You won't be forgiven
What's this
It's important that we enjoy expressing ourselves
Actually because we are eating
We shouldn' t be doing this
It's definitely just between the two of us
It is also important to understand the meaning of each word and its meaning in a novel.
Which one would be the best
This one
Anything will make me better
There are several ways, so I will explain them
You can do anything.
Maybe
There are non-verbal, emphasis and change forms.
Your appetite won over your desire to fight
Nonverbal is like direct verb or indirect verb
Or the active verse
Do you want to do something erotic with your teacher?
Like that
Emphasising form is
Repetitive form
Repeat same words to strengthen sentences
Strengthen your body.
Be connected to the content and improve your condition
Well, I'll do it if we eat a little more.
Exaggeration
Exaggerate more than in reality, or express it bigger or smaller
For example
Make a dot
Stubborn
Obey
Then I will explain about the change method
Say ah!
There are two ways to use the term.
Oh, no...
Wow, wow!
It's a bad sign!
My waist is moving...
It can be used for both job hunting and non-job hunting activities
Yama-chan!
Job hunting is relatively unnecessary
You're out of breath
Sorry
Did you get it?
Yes, I did.
You can't help but be patient anymore
OK then sit down
Oh yes
I'll do it.
Even though the teacher made it
Next
Adjective
To quote an old word
No, you don't have to
You're still going to be on TV?
Knowledge about the author or literature
It's your third time
Have knowledge of literary theory
Then when you feel better
[created using whisperjav 0.7]
When you get older, eat a lot of the food I made.
Aren'you nervous about it
Wait a minute.
Are you all right?
Are you all right, Yumi-chan ?
I'm going to be sucked up by that thing !
Chinchin is getting hard already
It's okay
Hold on
You're not supposed
Not yet.
Not yet?
No, not now...
Why can't you do that for me then ?
I've been watching a lot of things lately
and it's hard to keep up with them all at once
If it gets harder
Oh yeah
The teacher will tickle you
You're hungry aren' t you
Yeah
But before tha
there is something else
i want us too
What
Earlier
my tongue was stuck in your mouth
I want to give it back.
Give me back?
Really!
Why not
Look at this
You really love erotic things
Don't do that
You lick again
No,I don' t
Yama-chan
Because we'll give you lots to tickle
Make your chin more stiff
It'so warm
Why do you want me to give it back?
Does it feel good?
No, no.
You are energetic
I love this.
Go a little further.
It's getting bigger and bigger!
It's hard!
Can i see you
I'll go as far as possible to the end of this rope
Good
What happened to your neck
You want me to lick your nipples, don't you
Because he is really erotic
Doesn'it feel good
It's getting harder and harder.
Does it feel good?
It feels really good.
It's okay, it'll go all the way in.
Are you going to keep shaking like this?
You want to feel good right
You look like you're in a bad mood again, don't you?
I do
Can not stand it
Okay
Can I take this out?
What is it you want to take out, papa.
You want me to put it inside...
It's going to explode!
A little more.
You are tired, so I'll give you a milk panache
Are you sure?
Are you going to go out
It's a lie!
Did you get better?
Did it come out?
I think so, but my waist won't go up.
There are so many
It's not going up ?
Wait a minute
Are you okay
Maybe because I ate
But this is not enough
A lot came out
Oh no
I want to give you a lot.
Thank you for your hard work
Thank You
Then i have to return
Sorry
Next time we'll take proper showers
Please do
I love you.
Is it hard?
Thank you for your hard work today!
Does your hand feel so good that much, teacher ?
There was a person who is good at playing football, right?
Let me stroke more and more for you
Then let's go and find her
But she looks different from usual
What happened to me just now?!
I lost track of time.
Show us how much it feels
The original plan was to do it when you weren't here, right?
Yeah...
Let's go look for him then!
He should be somewhere around here somewhere
Are you going again
OK
Oh my gosh!!
You're back
It ended already??
Do not go
There were a lot of things going on so we got late
Did it end already...?
Were you lonely???
What!?
Wait, wait.
Great
It came out again.
It's already over?
There is something on your face!
Stop it and make me look pretty
Like this
How is it? Can you still take it out ?
Wait
What, can't you get our pants anymore
Wait a minute.
You're standing up, aren't you?
Do you want me to help you stand on your feet ?
Then I'll show you my favorite one
Please sit down
Are we good now
I can do it like this
Thanks for waiting
I'm glad you came to see me.
When we see this
You want to take them off again
You're so relaxed
So
Lie down
Are you comfortable?
Yes, but...
Your really love
Sensei's panties
What's your name?
Sato
Do you have a nosebleed
No
Yes, I do.
What's your name?
Well...
Read my name and say it
No
You're excited
Do you have to tell me my name
My namE is Ami
Ami-chan? You think it's you, don't you.
No...
See!
Let me see your tongue
Wow they are hard
It's the third time.
You look like a pervert again, don't you?
Show it to us
How do you feel about Ami chan
That is
What are those faces for
No, I'm fine.
You're feeling better?
Good for you!
Do you want to do it again ?
Your eyes are closed now
OK
Give me lots of hot noodles
Are you ready for that
Good
What do you usually say to me
Nothing special
Really ?
How about usual
Usual
Will you kiss my cheek
Do you want to do it?
No, I don't.
Great
You wanna try this one?
No...
This is the third time but I got most
Nope
It's gonna go deep
As promised
Let us eat
Let's kiss.
Let me use this
I can't study at all if you do this
Oh my god
Because your kisses feel good,
so it makes me want to do it right away
So let us be spoiled forever
Hey
Will you lend your lips?
It feels so good.
Show more tongue
What's this?
This is the best one I've ever had in my life, you know...
Your lips are really soft
Want a lot of kisses
Mom and Dad are coming home tomorrow, right?
Can you see how hard it is for me to chew on thing like that
So let's have a drink before that.
I'm looking forward to how many times you can do it!
You lick your favorite nipples so much
Oh no!
Wow
It has become an erotic stain
Let go of your hand
Wow
Do you want me licking directly
Okay
I'll lick it for you
I've never seen anything like this before.
Look at me carefully
When your poo is hard, I'll give you a lot of shiko-shiko again.
Oh, it's hot.
It's getting really hard...
Sensei loves your poo!
Because it gets bigger and bigger no matter how many times
I feel sick.
You want to go out, don't you?
Hey
Stand up because we're going to do something more pleasant
Yes...
Do you want me inside your body a lot ?
Is it OK for that...?
Oh! It'still there !
What do you mean by that ?!
No way !!
The poops in my mouth are getting bigger an d bigger
I just gave you an incandescent.
Make is even larger
Can you give it to me?
What's wrong?
No,I don't know...
What is this feeling...?
Do you feel good now ?
It's the first time for giving it out so..
Let try
You can do that right
It's getting harder and harder.
You can take it out now
You're full, aren't you.
You have a lot of hair on your face
Take it out
Wow, amazing
It is very thick
You're sweating, aren't you?
I've never seen you sweat this much.
Oh my god...
No! It's too late now!!
We can still do it
Why are you in such a hurry!?
Wait wait
I see
Can we make is work??
No no
Stop stop
He left
I'm done.
She grabbed my leg
Oh yeah
Just now
You used your legs a lot
This
Did you find it
Do usually use this kind
Yes,I did
You are the strongest in the world
Did you do it?
No
Am i okay now
Thank you for watching.
I'll use this to make you feel better.
I'm going to take a bath now!
[created using whisperjav 0.7]
Sit here and let me pet you a lot
Don't pet alone
If the teacher tells you,
You can always be petted
Wow
Did it go in?
Does your hand feel good too
Great sound
You're making a naughty sound.
Chinchin, Shiko-shiko
Does it feel good?
Are you going to go out of the room soon ?
It's okay! Let me pet your hand
He went out
He really went out
Did he feel good when I petted his hand
Hey
Hey, can you do it for me?
It feels good.
Come closer, please
It feels so good
It'so good.
I'm getting sleepy too...
Can you touch me?
Feels good, doesn't it!
You're doing great now
Ah, it feels good.
It feels so good!
Uh
Eh
Ehh
Uhh
No, no
It feels so good
I can'take it anymore
Give me your penis
Come here.
You like Shiko-shiko, but you also like Omanko too right?
I'll give you shikoshiku with sense's omanco
Does it feel good?
Your penis feels so good that I can't stop.
It feels so good!
Ah, it'so gross.
I'm going to go in there!
Ouch!
Your grandpa
has grown up so much
Can you make it bigger?
It tickles.
It feels so good.
Oh, no...
I'm going to puke!
It feels good
One more time
The doctor has left
So let me pat your back
Which one do you feel better?
Do you think it's going to be okay?
It is good.
You're sweating a lot
But the hand-in-hand manko felt better
I still want to do it
Hey hey
Follow me from behind
It'so hard even though I just took it out.
Ah, feels good!
It'so gross.
I'm going to tickle you with this toy
It feels good
Ouch!
Ouch, ouch.
Ouch
Which one feels better?
Massaging your eyes
or massaging your hands
Whichever feels better
Do you want to do it again?
To stroke your belly button one more time
Can I see the part of your stomach that is in pain
The part where my hands are stroking
Let's feel good together
Does it feel good
I want to do it while looking at your face.
Please tickle me a lot with your manko, Sensei!
Oh, no.
It feels so good there!
Hey...
Can you pet me more?
I want to be petted by your pussy and feel better together with you
Ah, it feels so good.
It feels so good!
I'm going to take a look at the place where you're going.
You were about go?
I'll tickle you.
Does it feel good?
Are you going to go out with me now ?
Let'see your face
You have a lot of pimples
Did that feels good for you
From now on
I'll give you a lot of kisses and pats.
Please keep it as our secret, okay?
[created using whisperjav 0.7]